Industrial Council of Coat, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Clipping Collection on Microfilm. 6155 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Industrial Council of Coat, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Clipping Collection on Microfilm
1925-1968
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
6155 mf
1.11 cubic feet
10 microfilm reels
Articles, news clippings, microfilm.
5821367
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 01, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 01, 2013
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Industrial Council of Coat, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers
5821367
- 1925-1930 (Reel 1)
- 1929-1935 (Reel 2)
- 1933-1941 (Reel 3)
- 1939-1945 (Reel 4)
- 1945-1948 (Reel 5)
- 1947-1951 (Reel 6)
- 1950-1954 (Reel 7)
- 1953-1958 (Reel 8)
- 1957-1965 (Reel 9)
- 1929-1940, 1964-1968 (Reel 10)